(Sheldon:)What? In the Chattahoochee
National Forest in Georgia?
(Sheldon:)I can't be the only one
that knows that's halfway.
(Beverley:)You're not seriously going
to visit each other.
(Alfred:)And why wouldn't we?
(Beverley:)Oh please, you're just saying
this to antagonize me.
(Alfred:)Oh, not at all. Mary happens
to be a wonderful woman.
(Alfred:)And if it antagonizes you,
that's just a bonus.
(Leonard:)Mary, I'm sorry you're
in the middle of this.
(Mary:)No, no, nothing to be
sorry about.
(Mary:)I genuinely like your father.
(Sheldon:)What? But he's a
mediocre academic.
And according to Beverly,
his sexual prowess is subpar.
(Sheldon:)He's basically Leonard
with a bigger prostate.
(Leonard:)Are you saying that my dad's
not good enough for your mom?
(Sheldon:)Yes, while also getting in
a solid dig at you.
(Sheldon:)Pretty efficient, huh?
(Leonard:)This is ridiculous.
I-I'm going across the hall.
(Sheldon:)But why should you get to go
and leave me here
(Sheldon:)with your bickering parents?
Fine, then you go!
(Mary:)Well, I don't want to stay
here with her. I'll go.